/* jshint esversion: 6 */

//Array of objecs which stores que and answer//

export const questions  = [
    {
        question: "Q.Which planet has 145 moons?",
        options:["Saturn","Mars","Mercury","Jupiter"],
        answer: "Saturn"
    },
    {
        question: "Q.In which country was the game of chess invented?",
        options:["India","China","Greece","Japan"],
        answer: "India"

    },
    {
        
        question: "Q.What was the first fruit to be eaten on the Moon?",
        options:["Grapes","A peach","A starfruit","Apple"],
        answer:"A peach"
    },
    {
        question: "Q.Which continent is home to the snow leopard?",
        options:["North America","Asia","South America","Africa"],
        answer:"Asia"

    },
    {
        question: "Q.What word appears on cold taps in Italy?",
        options:["Freddo","Froggie","Bruno","Carlo"],
        answer:"Freddo"

    },
    {
        question: "Q.Which country did Transylvania belong to from 11th century until 1918?",
        options:["Germany","Romania","Britain","Hungary"],
        answer:"Hungary"
    },
    {
        question: "Q.WHICH of these is NOT a recognised name for a young beaver?",
        options:["Mouse","Kit","Pup","Kitten"],
        answer:"Mouse"
    },
    {
        question: "Q.In Ancient Rome, how many days of the week were there?",
        options:["Five", "Eight", "Six", "Seven"],
        answer: "Eight"
    },

    {
        question: "Q.What is the primary gas that makes up the Earth’s atmosphere?",
        options:["Oxygen","Nitrogen","Carbon dioxide","Hydrogen"],
        answer: "Nitrogen"
    },
    {
        question: "Q.When was the world’s first ATM introduced, in Enfield, UK?",
        options:["1967","1977","1987","1997"],
        answer: "1967"
    },
];

